A Guide to the Laurance S. Rockefeller papers, Mary French Rockefeller papers FA1731
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Women's Interests, and Civic, Educational, and Religious Interests, 1932-1997; 1; 42.41 Cubic Feet 103 letter document boxes and 7 legal document boxes.
  - Brick Church - Fair, 1971-1977 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Brick Church - General, 1961-1970 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Brick Church - Program Committee, 1951-1959 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Calvin Coolidge Memorial Foundation, 1961-1992 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - A Christian Ministry in the National Parks, 1981-1984 (Box 69, Folder 3-4)
  - Connecticut College, 1959 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Foreign Policy Association, 1977-1989 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Foundation for Child Development, 1982-1983 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Foreign Policy Association, 1973-1983 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - New York Zoological Society, 1973-1981 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Union Church of Pocantico Hills, 1976-1986 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Union Board of Christian Education in Asia, 1989 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - United Service Organization (USO) of Metropolitan New York, 1980-1987 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Union Theological Seminary, 1979-1984 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - YWCA - 100th Anniversary, 1993-1994 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - YM-YWCA Camping Appeal Letters - MFR, 1995-1996 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - YWCA - National Board - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - YWCA - National Support - Miscellaneous, 1968-1984 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - YWCA - IBM - Thomas Watson, 1956-1990 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - YWCA - Hoover Worldwide Corp., 1967-1990 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - YWCA - National Board - Thank You, 1973-1986 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - YWCA - Nichols, Thomas S., 1964-1985 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - YWCA - Kettering, Ginny, 1982-1983 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - YWCA - RCA, 1982-1985 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - YWCA - Luce Foundation, 1968-1971 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - YWCA - McGraw-Hill, Inc., 1982-1989 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - YWCA - Rutherford-Bodman Foundation, 1962-1989 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - YWCA - Schiff, John, 1957-1991 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - YWCA - Zoltan, Hecht, 1957-1967 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - YWCA - Kyu Do Lee, 1963-1974 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - YWCA - Kirkland - Correspondence, 1944-1969 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - YWCA - Lillian Bean, 1970-1981 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - YWCA - Centennial Committee - Luncheon, 1969-1970 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Spelman College, 1978-1982 (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Spelman College - Dorcas Boit, 1963-1976 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - A Christian Ministry in the National Parks, 1986 September 10 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Von Hesse, Maxeda, 1984-1987 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - St. John the Divine - Award Dinner, 1976 November 10 (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Annual Appeals, 1961-1971 (Box 85, Folder 1-2)
  - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Annual Appeals, 1987-1996 (Box 85, Folder 3-4)
  - Bobst Foundation - Annual Meeting, 1988 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Foreign Policy Association, 1987-1990 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Foundation for Child Development, 1990 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Yellowstone National Park - A Christian Ministry in the National Parks, 1986 (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - YWCA, 1970 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - YWCA - New York City Centennial - Correspondence, 1970 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - MFR - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - YWCA - Asia Seminar - General, 1976-1978 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - YWCA - National Convocation on Racial Justice, 1972 (Box 87, Folder 2-5)
  - YWCA - White Plains, 1978 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - YWCA - White Plains, 1961-1981 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Spelman College - National Campaign, 1972-1981 (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Spelman College - Appeals for Funds, 1973-1979 (Box 88, Folder 3-4)
  - Spelman College - Board of Trustees, 1976-1979 (Box 88, Folder 5, Box 89, Folder 1)
  - YWCA - Convention, Boston, 1967 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - YWCA - National Board - Executive Management, 1973-1978 (Box 89, Folder 3-4)
  - YMCA-YWCA - Cooperation - Joint Project, 1967-1974 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - YWCA - Centennial, 1954-1955 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - YWCA - World Relations, 1971-1973 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - YWCA - Study Group - Christian Faith, 1964-1967 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - YWCA - World Relations Committee - Meeting, 1972 September 26 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - YWCA - Committee for Corporation and Foundation Support, 1965-1972 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - YWCA - National Board - Consultant - Women and Girls, 1961-1971 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - YWCA - National Board - Finance Committee, 1954-1972 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - YMCA-YWCA - Tarrytown, 1959-1962 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - YWCA - Overseas Consultation Staff Project, 1957-1958 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - YWCA - Centennial, 1970 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - YWCA - World Relations Unit, 1973 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - YWCA - World Service Council, 1992-1996 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - New York Ascendant - Report of the Commission of the Year 2000, 1987 June (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - China Institute in America - Annual Report, 1987 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary, 1992-1996 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - MFR - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1983-1992 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - YWCA - World Service Council - Executive Committee, 1992 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - YWCA - World Relations Committee, 1975-1982 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - YWCA - World Relations Committee, 1983-1992 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - YWCA - Convention - International Dinner, 1982 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - YWCA - World Relations Committee, 1980 January 9 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - YWCA - National Board - World Relations Unit, 1984-1985 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - YWCA - New York City - Board Materials, 1987-1989 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - YWCA - New York City - World Mutual Service, 1977-1994 (Box 93, Folder 3-4, Box 94, Folder 1-2)
  - YWCA - New York City - World Mutual Service, 1975-1976 (Box 94, Folder 3-4)
  - YWCA - New York City - World Mutual Service, 1981-1989 (Box 94, Folder 5-6)
  - YWCA - Board Materials, 1988-1996 (Box 95, Folder 1-2)
  - YWCA - National Board, 1952-1974 (Box 95, Folder 3-4, Box 96, Folder 1-2)
  - YWCA - Trips - Texas, California, Pittsburgh and Jacksonville, 1954 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - YWCA, 1950s (Box 96, Folder 4-5, Box 97, Folder 1-3)
  - YWCA - Board of Directors, 1984-1989 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - YWCA, 1980-1994 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - YWCA - Letters - Centennial Luncheon, 1955 January 11 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - YWCA - National Board, 1958 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - YWCA - World Service Executive Committee, 1987-1996 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - YWCA - National Board, 1993-1997 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - YWCA - Salute to Women Achievers Luncheon, 1995 November 9 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - YWCA - Thank-You Letters - Outdoor Program, 1996 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - YWCA - Convention Committee, 1953-1955 (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - YWCA - Home Advisory Council of New York, 1957 (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - YWCA - National Board - Finances, 1995-1997 (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - YWCA, 1984-1989 (Box 98, Folder 9-10)
  - YWCA, 1960-1991 (Box 98, Folder 11, Box 99, Folder 1-2)
  - YWCA - International Building Fund, 1992-1993 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - YWCA - ILEAD Meeting, 1990 February (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - YWCA - National Board - Mothers Centers, 1976-1991 (Box 99, Folder 5-6)
  - YWCA - World Service Council - Minutes, 1968-1976 (Box 99, Folder 7, Box 100, Folder 1)
  - United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia - Meetings, 1989-1991 (Box 100, Folder 2-4)
  - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary, 1989-1991 (Box 100, Folder 5-6, Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Philanthropic Activities, 1988-1991 (Box 101, Folder 2-3)
  - New York Community Trust - Board of Directors Meeting, 1991 July 25 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - James Foundation - Board of Directors Meeting, 1991 July 25 (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - YWCA, 1950s-1960s (Box 102, Folder 1-2)
  - YWCA, 1960s (Box 102, Folder 3, Box 103, Folder 1-3, Box 104)
  - YWCA - Publications, 1950s-1970s (Box 106, Folder 8, Box 107, Folder 1-3, Box 108)
  - MFR - YWCA Cards - Trips (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - YWCA, 1950s-1970s (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - YWCA - Camping Services, 1979-1992 (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - YWCA - Camping Services, 1973-1984 (Box 109, Folder 3-5)
  - YWCA - Camping Services, 1991 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - YWCA - Centennial Committee, 1954 (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - World YWCA - Year in Review, 1968 (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - YWCA - ILEAD Meeting, 1988 March (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - YWCA - National Board, 1994 (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - YWCA - Committee Reports, 1950s (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - Pledge Book, undated (Box 110, Folder 7)
  - YWCA - Publications, 1932-1996 (Box 110, Folder 8-9, Box 111, Folder 1-4, Box 112, Folder 1-5, Box 113, Folder 1-2)
  - YWCA - "Perspective" Publication, 1969-1976 (Box 113, Folder 3-5)
  - YWCA - Publications, 1970s (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - YWCA - Newsletter, 1970s (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - YWCA - National Board - "Looking to the Future", 1977 (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - YWCA - Camping Services - Report to the New York State Park Commission, undated (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - YMCA-YWCA Joint Planning Commission Report, 1972 (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - World YWCA Council Meeting, 1963 October (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - YWCA - Response to "YWCA: International Success Story", 1963 December (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - YWCA - Affirmative Action Guide to Equal Opportunity in the YWCA, 1979 January (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - YWCA - "One Imperative - Eliminate Racism", 1977 (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - YWCA - Publications, 1949-1964 (Box 115, Folder 1-2)
  - YWCA - Speeches, undated (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - YWCA - Notes, undated (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Spelman College - Charter, Bylaws, Report, and Newsletters, 1932-1956 (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - YWCA - Community Chest, 1952 (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - YWCA - Notes from Slides, undated (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary - Publications, 1979-1984 (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary - Publications, 1980s-1990s (Box 119, Folder 4, Box 120, Folder 1-2)
  - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary - Board of Trustees, 1976-1986 (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary - Board of Trustees, 1987 (Box 120, Folder 4-5)
  - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary - Board of Trustees, 1988 (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary - Board of Trustees, 1988-1989 (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary - Board of Trustees, 1990 (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary - Board of Trustees, 1997 (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Annual Appeals, 1993-1994 (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - National Institute of Social Sciences (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - Foreign Policy Association - Publications, 1978-1997 (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - Foreign Policy Association - Board of Directors, 1981-1983 (Box 122, Folder 1-2)
  - New York Community Trust, 1981-1997 (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - New York Community Trust - Publications, 1971-1991 (Box 122, Folder 4, Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Spelman College, 1954-1979 (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC), 1948-1950 (Box 123, Folder 7)
  - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Publications (Box 123, Folder 8)
  - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center (MSKCC) - Annual Appeals, 1984-1991 (Box 123, Folder 9)
  - James Foundation - Board of Directors, 1996 (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia, 1990-1996 (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - Lausanne Committee for World Evangelization, 1992 (Box 124, Folder 6)
  - Foundation for Christian Living - Founders Club Membership, 1989 (Box 124, Folder 7)
  - Foundation for Child Development - Annual Meeting, 1989 September 21 (Box 124, Folder 11)
  - United Nations Association of the United States - Annual Report, 1989 (Box 124, Folder 12)
  - Sidewell Friends School - Annual Report, 1989-1990 (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - National Geographic Article - South America - Responses to Article, 1967 (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - YWCA - Great Women - Letters Received, 1966-1967 (Box 126, Folder 2-3)
  - A Christian Ministry in the National Parks, 1986-1990 (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - Salute to the USO, Madison Square Garden, 1968 (Box 126, Folder 6)
  - United Nations and World Bank, 1960s-1970s (Box 126, Folder 8)
  - YWCA - Reports, 1976-1993 (Box 127, Folder 1-3)
  - YWCA - Newsletters, 1970s-1982 (Box 127, Folder 4-5, Box 128, Folder 1-4)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence and Reports, 1970s-1990 (Box 128, Folder 5)
- Personal papers and Family Interests, 1918-1997; 2; 17.45 Cubic Feet 41 letter document boxes and 4 legal document boxes.
  - Letters and Greeting Cards from Family - Birthdays, Holidays (Box 6, Folder 1-3)
  - Letters from Friends (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Mary French Rockefeller (MFR) - Donations, 1936-1969 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Mary French Rockefeller (MFR) - Donations, 1970-1991 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Mary French Rockefeller (MFR) - Contributions, 1946-1997 (Box 11, Folder 1-6)
  - Mary French Rockefeller (MFR) - China, Asia (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - New York City, 1986-1989 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Laura Rockefeller Case and Richard Chasin Wedding, June 14, 1956, 1956-1964 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Restricted - LSR Estate - Open in 2029
  - California and Hawaii Trip, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Mary French Rockefeller - Personal and Family Papers, 1943-1990 (Box 35, Folder 1-5, Box 36, Folder 1-4)
    Includes includes letters, cards, holiday greetings, newspaper clippings, correspondence.
  - Mary French Rockefeller - Personal and Family Papers, 1943-1991 (Box 37, Folder 1-3)
  - Marion's Debut, 1956 December 20 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Laura's Debut and Party, 1954-1956 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Children's Dances, 1951-1962 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Mary French Rockefeller - Candid Photos (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Rockefeller Family Fund - Report, 1996 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund - Annual Report, 1994 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Little Dix Bay Activities, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Random Reminiscences of Men and Events, John D. Rockefeller - Editor's Note, 2nd Draft, 1983 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Eastern Airlines - Board of Directors, 1983 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Woodstock Foundation - Annual Meeting, 1983 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Various Annual and Conference Reports, 1970s (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - MFR - General File, 1970s-1980s (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Woodstock, Vermont - General, 1974-1976 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Lady Bird Johnson, First Lady Trip, Virginia, 1965 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - MFR - Prayer Book, 1918 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - MFR - Prayer Book, 1928 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - MFR - Prayer Book, 1932 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Caneel Bay, Inc. - Meetings, 1980-1983 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Letters of Endorsement, 1947-1992 (Box 69, Folder 6-7)
  - French Anthology, 1954-1955 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - French Estate, 1957-1964 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Memberships, 1954-1958 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneious Data, 1940-1990 (Box 70, Folder 7-8)
  - Reader's Digest, 1964-1965 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller Family, 1957 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Rosemary Hall, 1965-1970 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Naomi Waletzky - Mayflower Ball, 1993 November 5 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    Restricted - LSR Estate - Open in 2029.
  - Larry Rockefeller and Wendy Gordon - Wedding, 1982 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - American Cancer Society - Luncheon, 1991 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - B, 1988-1997 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Elmer and Mamdouha Bobst Foundation, 1993-1995 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary - Appointments, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1949-1996 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - C, 1988-1996 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - D, 1989-1997 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Party at 834 Fifth Avenue, 1990 December 4 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - European Trip, 1993 May (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Federation of Protestant Welfare Agencies - LSR Award, 1991 October 28 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Foreign Policy Association - Dinner, 1993 May 27 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - H, 1989-1996 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Historic Hudson Valley - Event, 1993 June 12 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Hospital Chaplaincy - Dinner, 1992 November 10 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - I, 1993 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Letters, 1966-1975 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Dinner at 834 Fifth Avenue in Honor of Louis Marx, Jr. and Helen Zanetti Marx, 1992 October 29 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Albert Murray Retrospective, 1995 December 19 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - National Council of Negro Women, 1991 May 11 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Princeton University - Dinner, 1994 May 4 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Pocantico, 1960-1968 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Political Contributions, 1989 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Tarrytown, 1975-1977 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Family Christmas Luncheon, 1972 December 17 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Family Christmas Luncheon, Pocantico, 1989 (Box 74, Folder 6-7)
  - Union Church of Pocantico Hills - Dinner, 1991 November 22 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia - Luncheon, 1994 November 10 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia - Luncheon, 834 Fifth Avenue, 1995 November 8 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Matching Gifts, 1989 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Gifts - Laurance S. Rockefeller Charitable Trust, 1989 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Pledges, 1977-1987 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Invitations - Accept, 1969-1971 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Assistance - General Appeals, 1968-1978 (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Assistance - Scholarship Appeals, 1963-1988 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - African Enterprise, 1984-1989 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Katy G. Abbas - Katy Stanbro, 1986 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Bodine, Peggy, 1990 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Calvin Coolidge Memorial Foundation, 1988 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Cosmopolitan Club, 1961-1967 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Laura Carey and Reverend Benedict Hanson, 1979-1994 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Dallas YWCA, 1987-1988 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - E, 1990 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - F, 1971-1994 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Great Women - Letters Received, 1966-1968 (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Gordon-Conwell Theological Seminary, 1990 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Kampf, Ginny, 1982-1988 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Kivangere, Bishop (African Enterprise), 1987 (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Chilufya M. Konie, 1978-1980 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Korea Choir, 1969 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Kanter, Leela, 1980-1993 (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Lenox Hill Neighborhood Association, 1958-1968 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Little Sisters of Jesus, 1972-1973 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Ann Lowe, 1977-1981 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Project Maroula, 1963-1966 (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Margie Wolcott and Morton May, 1965-1972 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center - Lists, 1991 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Muller Office - Architect, 1990 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Muller, Robert, 1990 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - New York Blood Center, 1990-1992 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - A New England Pioneer, 1965 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - New York Zoological Society, 1975-1976 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Nurses, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Odongkara Family, 1978-1988 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Pacific School of Religion, 1988-1989 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Parties, 1946-1948 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Politics, 1980-1984 (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Invitations - Regret Letters, 1970-1981 (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Republican Party, 1979 (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Rosensteil - Restorations, 1982-1983 (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - Vananti Sarkar, 1969-1974 (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - Seeds, Frances, 1986-1991 (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - Thoughts and Meditations, 1960-1966 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Union Church of Pocantico Hills, 1958-1964 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - United Republican Finance Committee, 1963 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Mary French Rockefeller Giving Program - Matching Gifts, 1989 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Mary French Rockefeller Giving Program - Account Number 2, 1989 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Mary French Rockefeller Giving Program - Account Number 2 - A-Z, 1990 (Box 77, Folder 6-7)
  - Mary French Rockefeller Giving Program - Matching Gifts, 1990 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Mary French Rockefeller Giving Program - Matching Gifts, 1991 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Mary French Rockefeller Giving Program - Account Number 2 - A-Z, 1991 (Box 78, Folder 3-4)
  - Political Contributions - MFR, 1991 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Mary French Rockefeller Giving Program - Matching Gifts, 1992 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Mary French Rockefeller Giving Program - Account Number 2 - A-Z, 1992 (Box 79, Folder 2-3)
  - Mary French Rockefeller Giving Program - Matching Fund, 1993 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Mary French Rockefeller Giving Program - Account Number 2, 1993 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Mary French Rockefeller Giving Program - Matching Gifts, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Political - MFR, 1994 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Mary French Rockefeller - Giving Program - Account Number 2 - A-M, 1994 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Mary French Rockefeller Giving Program - Donor Advised Fund, 1995 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Mary French Rockefeller Giving Program - Contributions - A-L, 1995 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Mary French Rockefeller Giving Program - Contributions - M-Z, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Mary French Rockefeller Giving Program - Contributions - M-Z, 1996 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Mary French Rockefeller Giving Program - Foundation for New Era Philanthropy, 1995 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Political Contributions, 1996 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - National Center for Voluntary Action, 1977-1978 (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Vermont - General, 1959-1982 (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - Vermont - Contributions, 1965-1975 (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - New York Zoological Society - Luncheon, 1962 May 9 (Box 84, Folder 14)
  - Rosemary Hall Alumnae Award - MFR, 1977 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - MFR - Contributions, 1982-1984 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - National Parks and Conservation Association Dinner Honoring Larry Rockefeller, 1993 May 24 (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - Plumbridge, 1996 (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Alfred P. Sloan Jr. Memorial Award Dinner - LSR, 1969 (Box 105, Folder 1)
    Album of photographs and documents, including LSR's remarks on the occasion.
  - Rosemary Maung Sein Family, 1992-2000 (Box 105, Folder 2-4)
    Mary French Rockefeller befriended Rosemary Maung Sein during her visit to Myanamar in 1964.
  - MFR - Memorial Services and Condolence Cards, 1997 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Memorial Service for Eugene W. Kettering, 1969 April 21 (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - MFR - Contributions, 1991-1994 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - MFR - Contributions and Correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - MFR - Political Contributions, 1996 (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - In Mission - A Calendar of Prayer for the United Church of Christ, 1991-1992 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Elmer and Mamdouha Bobst Foundation, 1994 (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - Blue Hill Troupe, 1953-1955 (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - Arkasas Gazette, 1955-1956 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Rosemary Hall, 1952, 1953, 1956 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Pilgrim Dinner - Queen Elizabeth II, 1957 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Brown University Alumni Monthly on JDR Jr, 1960 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Williamsburg Award - Proceedings of the Presentation to Sir Winston Churchill, 1955 (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Frank Sinatra Dinner, 1982 (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Riverside Church Monthly, 1949 (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - Salute to Eisenhower Dinner, 1956 January 20 (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - Susan Edwards (Mrs. Robert F.) Wagner and Mary French Rockefeller at Gracie Mansion, 1956 (Box 116, Folder 11)
    Photograph.
  - United Nations, 1970 (Box 116, Folder 12)
  - UNICEF, 1976 (Box 116, Folder 13)
  - Bryn Mawr Alumna Bulletin, 1953 (Box 116, Folder 14)
  - Elizabeth Luce Moore, "Presbyterian Life", 1969 (Box 116, Folder 15)
    Friend of Mary French Rockefeller.
  - Vassar College, 1997 (Box 116, Folder 16)
  - Mary French Rockefeller - Trip Book, 1990-1994 (Box 116, Folder 17)
  - Mary French Rockefeller - Trip Book - China, 1985 (Box 116, Folder 18)
  - Caneel Bay, Inc. - Board of Directors Meeting, 1983 June 4 (Box 116, Folder 19)
  - United Nations - Study Guide - Advancement of Women, 1960s (Box 117, Folder 1)